ANH PHAN

Telephone Number: 0406 306 482 Email: myanhphan0806@gmail.com

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anh-phan-b830b845/

A Master of Analysis student with 5 years working in IT industry. As a digital content analyst and writer, I supported and optimised digital marketing strategy to help my clients enhance their online presence.

I am looking for a meaningful and challenging position in an organisation that allows me to face more practical opportunities and complete my skills as a business analyst besides academic knowledge.

Detailed portfolio:

Writing projects: http://anhphan0806.wixsite.com/content-writer-cv R projects: https://rpubs.com/anh_phan

EXPERIENCE

06/2013 - 08/2014

CONTENT WRITER CUM SEO - (WASHIN ENGINE CO. LTD.)

Washin Engine is a newly established company that has 100% Japanese capital investment. Its main scope of business includes website design, graphic design, SEO and business portal operation to support business expansion of Japanese enterprises in Vietnam.

- Wrote website contents (companies and news/ articles) in English and Vietnamese
- Found keyword list for Google Advertising campaigns
- Performed clients' website SEO audit and recommended content direction
- Created and kept track of customer database using Microsoft Excel
- Designed questionnaire to obtain customers' insight to develop the company's product

09/2014 - 02/2016

CONTENT EXECUTIVE - (PURE SOLUTIONS CO. LTD)

Pure Solutions is start up tech firm which consults and handles a spectrum of IT services including e-commerce, website and mobile application, and other corporate solutions.

- Produced VN- EN content for websites, press releases, video transcripts and social media
- Kept track of Facebook advertising campaigns' performance and reported to the supervisor
- Conducted research and analysis for projects and marketing activities
- Selected and edited images for more visually appealing content
- Worked closely with the development team as regard to websites updates

02/2016 - 09/2016

REGIONAL CONTENT EXECUTIVE - (SITEENGINE.CO. LTD)

Siteengine is a translation and website service company. Headquartered in Japan, Siteengine continues to expand its business in Thailand, Indonesia, Cambodia and soon Vietnam.

- Researched, translated and posted Vietnamese articles
- Proofread and helped to edit English articles
- Handled Facebook fanpage for the company's website

09/2016 - 07/2018

CONTENT EXECUTIVE - (AMBITION+ CUSTOM SOLUTIONS PTY LTD)

Ambition+ Custom Solutions is a Vietnam-based offshoring outsourcing company that works for Australian clients. The company specialises in website development, custom built software development with the focus on automotive industry.

- Received customer briefs on new projects, coordinated the team and the supervisor for the proper execution
- Researched and generated quality content across platforms (websites, social media and email marketing)
- Took part in building database and manage relevant product data and its quality
- Worked with the development team to make sure SEO practices are implemented on newly developed codes
- Conducted SEO reports to clients (competitor and SEO performance analysis, keyword research and digital strategy)
- Wrote blog posts geared towards users' interests to promote clients' products and services
- Assisted the team with basic designing and coding jobs for content updates

EDUCATION

[02/2010] - [12/2012]

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE - (RMIT, HO CHI MINH CITY, VIETNAM)

GPA: 3.0/4.0

[07/2018] - [06/2020]

MASTER OF ANALYTICS - (RMIT, MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA)

SKILLS

- IT languages: R, Python, SQL, and ASP.net
- Project Management: Trello, and Confluence
- Design: Photoshop
- SEO: Yoast, HTML and Google Analytics
- Teamwork
- Attention to detail and multi-tasking skills
- Good analytics and research skills
- Good time management skill

REFERENCES

(Available upon request)